Downloaded @ subs4free.club
You up?
What time is it?
Uh, late.
Oh, yeah, I guess I am up.
Oh.
Uh, the lake's gonna
be so good today.
Yeah... Yeah.
Don't worry about amber.
She likes you better.
No, she doesn't.
I'll just be you.
She likes you, too.
She actually does.
Plus, I'm gonna
be there as well.
It'll be fine.
I need to wear this though.
Stop taking my clothes.
Okay, mom. Oh my
god, get up, let's go eat.
Thank you, got you.
Um, I'm just gonna
call my mom real quick.
Okay.
Debra johnson.
Hi mama.
Oh good, kara, it's just you.
I got scared I forgot a meeting.
Um, cool.
I just wanted to tell you
really quickly that jess and I are
Gonna go over to
amber stole's lake house,
And I'll probably be back
by, like, ten or ten thirty.
Hey, is the whole gang there?
Is ryan going with you?
No, he's got practice all day.
Oh, that's a shame.
What a waste of a beautiful day.
Wish I could be
at the lake myself.
Um, I also just wanted to remind
you that I'm gonna go over to
Dad's really early on Saturday.
What? Why?
Just so, like, katie and jess
and I can go see a movie.
And dad's just gonna pick
us up, so jess will drop me off
Afterwards and
it'll be no biggie.
Oh right, of course, I...
Would you rather
I didn't do that?
No, no, no, no, it's fine.
Don't worry about it.
You have a good time today.
When you get home tonight,
if I'm not there, don't wait up.
I have a date.
And you can tell
your father that.
Okay, sounds good.
I love you. Bye mama.
Love you, too. Bye.
Yes. Um, my mom did say
we have to water the plants,
But then we can go.
Okay, good to go then?
I have to take a shower.
Okay, go shower.
Do you want me to water
the plants? Mm-hmm.
Okay, I'll do it.
Is it front yard and
back yard? Mm-hmm.
I'll do it. Thank
you, you're the best.
See you in 15.
Hi there.
Hi.
Are your parents home?
No, actually this
isn't my house.
This is my friend's house.
Okay, um, what about her
parents, are her parents home?
No, her mom's not home.
Ah, can you just hold onto
these for me? Oh yeah, sure.
Good.
If you scream, I'm
gonna shoot you.
You're gonna come with me.
Let's go.
Stay there.
Get in the container now!
Get your head down.
Don't you say a word.
Five seven two nine
one eight dash b.
Okay, let's go.
Now who's not ready to go?
Kara!
Those plants are getting
a better shower than me.
Where are you?
Kara! Kara!
Sit up.
I'm gonna restrain you.
I'm gonna tie you up at
the wrists and your ankles.
I'm gonna gag you.
And I will always
have this gun on me.
Do not make me use it.
Okay.
Don't move.
Escape.
No!
Wait.
Wrists.
Open your mouth.
Lie back, sit back.
Put your feet
out in front of you.
Debra johnson.
Mrs. Debra, did you
come to pick up kara?
Jess?
You came to get her, right,
for some, some emergency?
What?
I thought the two of you
were going to the lake together.
Kara's not here.
What are you talking about?
I just spoke to her.
But not to come pick her up?
Jess, where is kara?
I'm gonna take you
out of the car now
And you're not gonna
make any noise.
I still have my gun.
Where is it? Where is it?
Ryan, ryan.
Hello.
Ryan, is kara with you?
Miss johnson?
Is kara there?
She's at jess's.
Though they might have
already left for the lake.
I'm sure she'll give you
call whenever they get there.
Ryan, kara has gone
missing from jess's.
I'm on my way over there now.
Missing?
I got to call the police.
Miss johnson, miss johnson.
Sit up.
I'm gonna take off
all your restraints,
And you're gonna get out.
And I might take the gag out
if you promise not to scream,
Yell, or be loud.
Hmm?
Shhh.
Feet.
Come with me.
Straight ahead.
In.
Stand by the bed and face me.
I'm gonna lay out the rules
for while you're here now.
One, I will always
have this gun,
Or some other weapon nearby.
Two, you will
always call me daddy.
Three, you will listen
to everything I say
And do everything
that I tell you to do.
If you want anything, you'll
have to ask for permission.
And most important, if
you break any of the rules,
There will be
consequences, understood?
Understood?!
Yes.
Yes, daddy.
Sit down.
What's your name?
Kara.
Last name.
Robinson.
How old are you, kara robinson?
I'm 15.
Where do you live?
I just live in lexington.
Two-two-zero willow spring road.
Who else lives there?
Just my mom.
What's her name?
My mom's name's debra.
What about your dad?
Um, they're separated, so.
Oh, that can be so
hard on the child.
Then again, sometimes
it's for the best, isn't it?
What's his name?
Ron.
Where does he live?
Eighty-one elm lane.
Your friend whose house
you were at, what's her name?
Jess.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Yeah.
And what's his name?
Ryan.
How long have you been dating?
About a year.
Have you had sex with ryan?
No.
Have you had sex
with anyone else?
No.
What about oral sex, or have
you done things with your hands?
Are you in love with ryan?
Yeah.
Wow, so that's
what makes him real.
Do you love jess?
Yeah.
Do you love your mom and dad?
Do you think they miss you?
Lay down on the bed.
Do it!
Be quiet.
Follow the rules.
Wait.
Survive.
Gather information.
Get in.
Hello.
Rob.
Debra.
Look, I, I told kara she could
contact me if she needed me,
But I, I thought we agreed
you just tell her what you need
To tell me, okay.
So, kara's not there with you?
Debra, why would she be with me?
I'm five hours away
and I'm working.
What's going on?
Kara's gone missing.
What do you mean?
She's missing, ron.
She disappeared
from jess's yard.
Somebody...
Oh god.
Somebody must have taken her.
Oh, my god.
Look, okay, I'm come,
I'm coming back right away.
I'll come right there.
Okay, I'll, I'll see you soon.
Okay.
And about how long did
you say she's been gone?
Missing, she's been missing
for about two hours now.
And you didn't hear anything?
No.
Don't you think
she would tell you?
She's answered your
questions multiple times, sir.
Well, ma'am, we'll see if the
neighbors have anything to say.
But chances are,
your girl is a runaway.
My daughter is the
most responsible. Ma'am.
The idea that she would
runaway at all without her, her, her,
Her purse, without her
clothes, without her shoes!
Kids do dumb things, ma'am.
Even if she did
runaway, without a thing,
Without telling another
soul in this world, she is 15!
You need to find her.
I'm sorry, I will
file this report.
Officers will know
to be on the lookout.
You should go home.
Wait and see if she calls.
Wait, escape, survive.
You look good in my shirt.
So, where do you go to school?
Kenaston high.
Do you like it?
Uh, yeah.
Gather information.
Did you like going
to high school?
Yeah, for the most
part, I guess I did.
It's easy when
you're a good student.
I graduated early.
Oh, you must be
really smart then.
I like to think so.
Did you, like, do
anything after, like,
Did you go to
college or anything?
No, too expensive.
I had some part-time
jobs when I was in school,
But nothing saved up.
Actually, I joined the navy.
Oh, the navy.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, cool.
Nine years.
They wouldn't give me
the promotion I deserved,
But they did give me
a bunch of medals and
An honorable discharge.
That's impressive.
You know I'm not
looking to hurt you.
Not if you don't make me.
I'm gonna let you go
when I'm finished with ya.
Breathe, wait.
Escape.
No, no!
Wait.
Have you smoked before?
Uh, no.
Well you're gonna.
Inhale deep and hold it.
Come on.
Follow the rules.
That's good.
Go again.
Wait, could you show me?
Do you have, like, some
kind of, like, technique?
Yeah.
Could you show me one more time?
Now, kara, remember
there are rules.
I think you're trying to do
something that you don't
Have permission to do.
Uh-uh. Hmm.
And when you break the
rules, there are consequences.
You were so good, kara,
that you have earned a reward.
How many animals do you have?
Go see for yourself.
Do you have a favorite?
Hmm.
Probably clyde,
the gray cockatiel.
I've had him the longest.
But I like them all, or
they wouldn't be here.
Have you always liked animals?
I guess so, yeah.
They're easy to figure out.
Happy to be kept.
Do you work with animals?
Now that you don't work
in the navy anymore?
No.
I have a boring job.
I work with air compressors.
Do you like it enough?
Yeah, I like it enough.
Cool. Not as much as the
navy, but all over the country.
Where do you like to go?
San diego's nice, especially
since I used to live there.
I am gonna let you
go when I'm done.
But what happens
next is up to you.
If you go and report me,
You will always be the
girl who was raped, forever.
Sit down.
We are going to
watch this together,
And I want you to
tell me all about it.
Wait.
Escape.
Hi gretchen, it's debra.
Yes, kara's mom.
I got your number from...
Oh, you've heard.
The police said they're not
worried yet, but we, yeah.
We're just trying to get people
out all over to look for her.
Uh, the only thing we have
to go on is a neighbor saw
A black trans am.
I'm going to be here by the
phone and you can always, um,
Call into the lexington
sheriff's department.
Thank you, gretchen.
Bye.
May I please go to the bathroom?
Of course.
Escape.
Go ahead.
Stop.
Ask permission.
May I wash my hands, please?
Daddy.
Yes, you may.
Sit, I'm making dinner.
You'll have to eat
while you're here.
I understand.
I just, I don't really feel
like eating right now.
Remember there are
consequences if you don't do
What I tell you to.
Okay.
Is there anything that I could
do for you while you're eating?
Yeah, you can sweep
the floor, just the kitchen.
Broom's right there.
Stop.
Take that off.
Follow the rules.
A black trans am.
That her friend's car?
No.
Ma'am, I've got kids of my
own, and I don't think there's ever
Been a time where I
knew all their friends,
Let alone their friend's cars.
Do you always know where your
daughter is and who she's with?
No, I don't.
But I do know that kara
would never go this long without
Calling unless something
was keeping her from it.
She's not just any kid, sheriff.
Somebody get me detective munro.
It has been much too long.
I'm gonna get my best
people on it, all right?
Thank you.
All right then.
But I need you to do something.
You've done your job.
I apologize it took
you coming in.
But the best thing you
can do, well, the only thing
You can do really is to
go home and wait for a call.
Sit down.
Let's see if anyone misses you.
As you said, bob,
the story is still holding
Everyone's attention tonight.
This afternoon, shocking high
speed chase through downtown,
One that may turn deadly,
As one victim
remains in the hospital.
The brown sedan tore around
the corner of washington avenue
And main street.
Wow, not the lead story.
It's sad, really so sad.
I'm gonna let you
go and no one cares.
Not ryan, not jess,
not your mom and dad.
You loved them so much,
and not a one of them cares.
Get up.
Get up!
Wait, escape, survive.
Uh!
Stand over there.
I need to make a phone call.
You're gonna get
back in the container,
I'm gonna put the gag
back in your mouth,
And you're gonna stay there
and you're gonna be quiet.
Uhh.
Get in the container.
Get in!
Open your mouth.
Lean back.
Wait, escape, survive.
Breathe.
Wait, breathe.
I can't breathe.
I can't breathe!
Why are you making noise?!
Answer me!
I don't know.
What?
Okay, I, I'll leave the lid
off and take the gag out,
As long as you stay quiet.
Uh-huh.
Lie down.
Lie down!
But you have to be quiet.
Or there will be
real consequences.
Survive.
You were very
good at being quiet.
Anxiety can be really tough.
I've had it before.
This helps me.
Take it.
Did you swallow it?
I think so.
Good.
Wait, escape, information.
Good night.
Time for bed.
Escape!
No, no, no!
Wait.
Ladies first.
And I still got to tie you
up before I go to sleep.
These will help keep you
from getting any stupid ideas.
Wrists.
We have a big day tomorrow.
Escape.
Come on, go, come on.
Escape!
Hey, hey, hey!
Please, please!
I got kidnapped!
I was kidnapped!
What do you want us to
do? It was that apartment.
Could you take me to
the police station, please?
Please.
Get in. Thanks.
It was that apartment.
I need you to remember
that for me, please.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, thank you.
Gotta get justice.
My name is kara robinson.
I was kidnapped
and then I escaped.
Miss robinson?
Kara, k-a-r-a r-o-b-I-n-s-o-n.
I think you should
write that there.
I thought it'd be more... I was
kidnapped and then I escaped.
Have a seat, miss robinson.
Just in those chairs over there.
Okay.
Miss. Hi, your name.
Kara.
Hi kara.
Um, may I?
Yeah.
Kara, my name's
lieutenant rowland.
You can call me aaron. Okay.
May I ask what's happened?
I was kidnapped
yesterday by a man, white,
Medium build with brown hair,
with a gun yesterday morning,
And then I, um, he
raped me multiple times,
And then I escaped this
morning while he was asleep,
In those handcuffs and this.
Okay.
Um, how, how did you get here?
I stopped a couple
of men, big men, like,
In the car and they
drove me over here.
Kara, I'm gonna have
a word with the corporal,
And then I would like to hear
everything you can remember,
If that's all right
with you. Yeah.
Are you comfortable coming
in my office? Mm-hmm.
Okay, follow me. Okay.
Okay, have a seat,
I'll be right in. Okay.
Get another inspector in here.
I need a missing person's
report for kara robinson and
The drivers interviewed,
and update the sheriff.
Okay, kara, thank
you for waiting.
Can you start at the beginning?
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Hi, hi, did you bring a girl
into the station just now?
Yeah, is she okay?
We have to go to work, but.
We're taking care
of her, don't worry.
We just need to
know where exactly
Did you pick her up from.
The beachwood
commons apartments,
Right off the 20/26 exchange.
Great.
And can you tell me which unit?
We can't remember.
I mean it was just a girl
coming out of nowhere.
It's all right.
I got off the bed, so I
could put my shorts back on,
And then I saw that
there was this big, like,
Lock thing on the door, and I
knew it was gonna make a bunch
Of noise, so I just opened
it as quick as I could,
And then I ran, and then I
saw the guys in the car, like,
Waved them down.
I, I just talked to them.
Sergeant bonnie jennings.
I'm gonna be working
with lieutenant rowland
Here on your case.
I did find this in the system.
You were first reported
missing almost 18 hours ago.
Debra johnson,
that's your mother?
Yeah.
Hello.
Miss johnson, this is lieutenant
rowland with the richland county
Sheriff's department.
Is it kara?
Yes, ma'am, we have
your daughter here.
Is she okay?
Mom, momma can
you come pick me up?
Oh baby.
Baby, I'll, I'll be
right there, okay.
I'm coming right now.
Okay, mrs. Johnson.
I have a tough
thing to ask, kara.
Do you think that if we
went back to the complex
You'd be able to pick
out the apartment?
Oh, I asked the people
in the car to remember
What the apartment number was.
I asked them, and I'm sorry
to say they didn't remember.
I think they were pretty
distracted by the sight of you.
I don't think I'm
gonna remember.
Kara, would you be up
to coming back with us
To give it a try anyway?
Get justice.
Get him.
Yeah.
I think we're close.
I think this is it.
Anything looking familiar?
Uh, yeah, I just... It
just looks the same.
Maybe this guy can help.
Excuse me, sir.
Richland county sheriffs.
We're looking for the
apartment of a man here.
Mid 30s, caucasian, brown
hair, about five foot nine.
Uh, sorry, it's a big complex.
A lot of guys could be
that, especially if you include
Boyfriends and
relatives, you know.
Yeah, okay, thank you.
All of his windows
are covered up.
He's got like a wolf
curtain kind of over his bed,
And he lives with a
lady with long blond hair.
I'm sorry, miss, I... He also
had a wall full of animals.
He had birds, rats,
hermit crabs, guinea pigs,
That type of stuff.
A lot of fish, too.
Oh, yeah, that's
apartment 301, yeah, 301.
Would you mind showing
the sergeant here to the leasing
Office, so we can pull
the info on that unit?
Yeah, sure.
Thank you.
Kara, let's get you back.
That's great work.
This is lieutenant rowland,
I need a car watching 1532
slaw street, apartment 301.
Suspect is considered
armed and dangerous.
Sergeant jennings
is watching the scene.
Copy that lieutenant.
We'll put an all
points bulletin asap.
Officer please respond.
Officers please-
Kara, where is she? Ma'am?
Kara robinson. Mrs. Johnson.
Yes, you called me.
You called me to tell
me that she's here.
What and, and she's not?
I don't know, I-
What do you mean you don't know?
Where the hell is my daughter?!
Momma.
Oh, my baby.
What's the word?
No activity in the unit
since patrol showed up,
And none of the neighbors
witnessed him leaving.
Could be holed
up, waiting for us.
Could be.
Let's go see.
Police!
Can I have the keys?
Clear!
Clear! Clear!
All clear.
This is the right spot.
She was spot on.
Jennings. I'll get the bolo out.
And get kara to make that id.
Yes, sir.
Do a sweep of the area.
Surrounding buildings,
parking lots, any suspicious man.
Get the technicians here.
You'll have those additional
search warrants asap.
Yes, sir.
Can't believe they
have kept us waiting.
I'm going to get you something.
I'm fine.
No, I'm going to say something
and I'm going to get them to-
No, please just stop, please.
Are you hungry?
Are you, are you thirsty?
Are you...
Miss johnson.
Hi there. We haven't met yet.
I am sergeant jennings.
I'd like to give you some
pictures to look at and
See if your
kidnapper's in there.
If you're up for it.
Yeah, of course.
Number four.
You're sure? Number four.
That's the man that is leasing
the apartment that you were in.
Um, his name is
richard marc evonitz.
Unfortunately, he was gone
by the time we got there.
Are you saying he's
still out there? Mom.
We've got everyone
out there looking for him.
He's not gonna get far.
Oh, well, everyone's looking
out for him, that's reassuring.
Kara, if there is anything
that you think you might know,
Or any information that you
have that might help us figure out
Where evonitz is going.
Yeah, he was honorably
discharged from the navy
At least a couple of years ago.
And the gray
parakeet that he has,
Actually I think it's a
cockatiel, um, his name's clyde,
And he's had it longer
than any of his other pets.
Uh, the woman that he lives
with is probably in disney world
Right now with somebody else,
so he's got to go back to work
Tomorrow, something to
do with, like, air compressors.
Family doctors
name is dr. Reitz,
And the phone number
for that is 803-555-6714,
And he's a got a
history of anxiety,
And he's got a dentist as well
whose name is dr. Greg nublin
And the number for that is
803-555-8562, 803-555-856, yeah.
There's a box, a big box, too,
underneath all of his animal
Cages that he did not
want me to know about,
So you should probably
find whatever that is,
You should find that.
We will. Be sure to do that.
In fact, would you mind
calling that all in right now?
Thank you.
While the detective is
updating lieutenant rowland,
I'd like to talk through
some of what comes next.
Okay.
Two specially trained
nurses are gonna come in,
They're gonna
collect your clothes,
And any other relevant
evidence, you know.
First thing we have to do is
we have to ask you some more
Detailed questions
about what happened.
Okay. Okay?
Mom, could you go outside
for this part, do you think?
Uh, of course, baby.
I'll just be in the hallway
if you need anything.
Okay, kara, you ready?
Yeah.
Sir, what's in here just
keeps getting worse.
And no sign of evonitz.
No, sir.
Did find a vehicle registered
in his name, a taurus,
Not the trans am.
Bolo's been updated with
kara's id, but no hits yet.
Let's damn well hope whatever
he's hiding in his foot locker
Is something useful.
We have bolt cutters in here.
Gonna need some evidence bags.
That's the outfit that kara
described him wearing.
Those aren't?
No, no, they're not kara's.
Officer, you get me everything
you can find on these cases,
And the number to the
spotsylvania county sheriff.
Those notes decipherable?
Some, these, these
might be directions.
Figure it out, lieutenant.
Use whatever you need,
and find this son of a bitch.
Have you ever been to
a gynecologist, honey?
No.
Okay, the next thing
that we need to do here is
A pelvic exam, all right?
Okay, all right.
If you could just
scooch forward,
Lie down and raise your knees.
Okay, here we go.
Get through this.
Get justice.
Please take this,
he's dangerous.
Seen this man? No, no.
No. But, okay, I'm
gonna put this up back.
Okay, perfect.
Have you had any
updates from your people?
Nobody's seen head
or tail of this guy.
I heard you want with the feds.
They got a lead?
No. What we do have is
more information from the fbi
And the silva/lisk task force
on the spotsylvania cases.
Sophia sylva, age 16,
was snatched off her
Own front porch.
The police worked
it as a runaway.
The body wasn't
found 'til months later.
We put the wrong guy away
for it in an uproar to bring justice
To the girl, and not even
a year later two other girls,
12 and 15-year-old sisters are
grabbed from their front yard.
This man holds
these children for days,
Then he drowns them in his
bathtub and dumps their bodies
In the swamp.
That task force has been
working those cases for five years.
I'm not gonna say it's evonitz
before the evidence is in.
Hell, I'll say it.
Evonitz is a serial
killer of little girls.
The papers in the foot locker
were mostly full of stalking
Notes, potential victims
from the looks of it.
But we've been able to
track down all the most recent
Targets, they're okay.
Was the robinson
girl in those notes?
Kara, no she wasn't.
The girl we think it was
meant to be went to a friend's
Instead of walking home.
That makes you think about what
other cases could be out there.
You put some of my guys on that.
I mean there's no way evonitz
started with those murders.
Sheriff, sheriff, we've
gotten hold of the woman
With the long blond hair.
Evonitz's wife, ashley.
She and evonitz's mother
are exactly where kara said,
Disney world.
They're headed
back to cooperate.
Well that's good news.
We've also got the mother's
okay to search her house.
And one of the sisters is
coming in tomorrow to answer
Some questions, too.
I only pray that she's got
something worth telling.
You and me both.
Kara. Kara.
Hey.
Hey, that's okay, it's not
your fault, jess, it's not your.
Oh, sweetheart.
I want to go home.
Are you okay?
Can you tell me what happened?
Where were you?
Do you know where you were?
Can you stop asking
questions, please stop.
Kara, honey, I, I
just, you can tell me,
You can tell me anything.
I want you to tell me.
You don't want to know,
so just... Just don't ask
If you don't want
to know the answer.
Any sign of him? Not a one.
Seems like he just came by
to drop his momma's car off
And take her other one.
I've updated the bolo, but
he's switched cars once,
I'm sure he's done it again.
No, you're likely right.
Fbi's on its way out to
take control of the evidence
Collection themselves.
I wouldn't be surprised if they
just end up shipping the thing
Straight to quantico.
That thing's gonna have
some evidence of those
Virginia girls, I'd
put money on it.
Maybe we'll find some
stash of his in the house.
Maybe.
It's hard to take comfort
in closing cold cases when
He's still out there
to make new ones.
Listen, I'll stay here
and wait for the feds.
I want you to go and
check in with kara.
She should know where
we're at with the search.
Okay.
Oh, hey.
Hello.
Come on in.
Hey, thank you so
much for coming over.
This means a lot.
My mom's just,
like, in the kitchen
If you're looking for her.
Okay.
Hey, kara, you're a tough
girl to get an audience with.
I can't do this anymore.
Okay, come on.
How can I help?
Why are the police still here?
Like, what's going on?
Some of the officers are
here for your protection
Because we don't know
where evonitz is yet.
We just need to take
that extra precaution.
There are a lot of officers
across both counties,
And now the fbi involved.
So, sometimes they
might be showing up here
For information, or updates.
But the final reason
is understanding.
You know, they all know you
escaped something on your own,
So they're impressed, or
curious, or just concerned.
It's the same reason why you
see people here who you've never
Seen in this house before today
just showing up with apologies
And pecan bars.
But I don't want that, I
don't want any of this.
I can certainly understand that.
That is not fair to you.
You have every
right to be angry.
But it just comes
down to people caring.
Thank you, sergeant.
I think I'm just gonna
go lie down for a little bit.
That's not a bad idea.
Okay.
And then maybe you'll
catch him tomorrow and
Everything will
go back to normal.
Maybe.
Might take a little while
longer than tomorrow, kara.
But sleep is
always a good start.
I think I'm gonna go over
to ryan's after breakfast.
You're not going anywhere.
They still haven't caught
that horrible man, and,
And they're here to keep watch
'cause he could be out there
Looking for you, anybody could.
I was allowed to go to ryan's
whenever I wanted without
Asking you, like, two days ago.
That was two days ago.
What's different now?
Kara. No for real,
what's different now?
I don't need protecting.
I got back here all by myself,
I'm not gonna stop acting
The way that I used to
act because of all of this.
This isn't my life.
It's just something
that happened.
No, we're not done
discussing this.
You are not leaving this house.
Is it, is it okay that I came?
Yeah, I'm so glad
you're here right now.
Let's go to my room.
Do you want to do
our nails or something?
I can get my nail polish.
Uh, yeah, whatever
you want to do.
Just ask.
Ask what?
Just ask what you
really want to ask.
No.
No, I just wanted to see you.
To see if you were okay.
As, as okay as you can be.
I'm okay.
Really, I'm okay.
Just ask.
What happened?
A man pulled into the driveway.
He sent me to disney
because he's a good man.
Marc couldn't
have done all that.
I'm sorry to say he did, ashley,
and if we can't track him down,
He might do something else.
So, do you have any idea
where your husband might be?
No.
He says he's happiest
when he's with me.
If he's not at his mom's.
He hasn't tried to call
you or contact you at all?
No.
But he loves me no matter what,
and I love him no matter what.
Okay.
Hi mama.
Hi ashley. Stephanie?
Hi.
I'm sure they just called
her in like they did us, honey.
From what I know
he's in ashley's car,
But he told me he
switched the plates.
They were still
south carolina, I think.
He's probably gonna find a
way to contact one of us soon.
He's trying to find a
way to get ashley to him.
I have a feeling that this
is not the first time marc
Has done something
like this with a young girl.
Finding out the brother you care
about isn't who you thought is a
Tough thing, stephanie, but
you have done good talking to me.
Marc contacted me
yesterday afternoon.
I'm sorry.
Sheriff, evonitz is at this
motel outside of orangeburg.
The room is under his
sister's name, stephanie newell.
She hasn't talked to him since.
He should still be there.
Not check out yet.
Jennings, get down there.
I'll get orangeburg sheriff
to send a team asap.
Copy.
Oh, just ignore them.
So you're still gonna
come and pick me up
Later for the game, right?
Um, yeah.
Okay. Of course, same as always.
Well hello there.
I'm here to talk to your mom.
Sheriff stevens, lexington
county. Right on, yeah, she's inside.
Hmm, how are you doing?
Good, I'm fine.
You've been through a
hell of an ordeal, young lady.
You've been victimized.
You ought to take
some time to recover.
You really shouldn't be out
and about when we haven't
Caught your attacker yet.
Maybe you should get
out there and catch him.
You certainly didn't help
me the first time around.
You know that guy
was gonna kill you, right?
And all things said, you
should be dead right now.
He's likely killed
at least three girls.
Now the evidence hasn't
come in yet, but it will.
You should thank your lucky
stars that you weren't next.
Luck had nothing to do with it.
Well, evonitz
wasn't at the motel,
But it looks like
he left in a hurry.
The shirt kara was wearing
when he took her is here,
And some of his clothes, too.
Orangeburg's agreed to keep
surveillance on the room in case
He comes back, but I think
he's probably on the move.
Okay, make sure that
evidence gets where it ought
And come on back.
One of the family
tipped him off.
Probably, but at least we
know for sure he's running,
Not stalking kara or
some other girl, running.
Yeah, at least for now.
At least for now.
The fbi sent the prelims on
the fibres from the handcuffs,
It's looking like a match
to the fibres found on
All three bodies, and
there's a full palm print
On the inside of the trunk.
Between that and
his sister's statement.
I know.
An entirely off the radar
serial killer done in by his
Intended victim,
it's incredible.
Hello kara.
Jim price, sheriff
for richland country.
Are you gonna tell
me to stay inside, too,
Because you haven't done
your job yet and my attacker
Is a serial killer?
I'd never presume to
tell you what to do, kara.
Even if I thought evonitz
was a threat to you, and I don't.
I won't ask who told
you about our suspicions
Since it doesn't matter.
What does matter is what you
know and what you want to know.
Did he kill those three girls?
We can't say for certain yet.
What we know was in the
foot locker you pointed out,
Were articles discussing the
disappearance and murder of
Three girls around your age
from about five years ago.
Why would he have
those if he didn't kill them?
That's a good question, but
someone was wrongly accused for
The first girl's murder,
which is why I make it a point
To wait on the evidence.
Would he have killed me?
I can't say that.
But even if he wanted to,
you didn't give him the chance.
So, the reason I
came looking for you.
I needed to come and say
thank you for the incredible
Thing you've done.
Some people will try to
tell you you're a victim,
But you really
are is a survivor,
One with a kind of strength
and grace that's rare in this world.
We may not have your captor
yet, but we're going to get him.
And when we do, it will
be because of you, kara.
Thank you.
You're welcome, I guess.
You let me know if there's
anything I can do for you.
And if you wouldn't mind,
I'd love to come by and
see you sometime again.
See you around then, sheriff.
Sheriff price.
Evonitz used his cell
phone about 15 minutes ago
Just outside of
jacksonville, florida.
Now, we're guessing he's
headed to see his other sister.
She's about three hours
further south in bradenton.
Okay, this is it.
You make sure the police
in jacksonville and bradenton
Are up to date.
I'll call state myself.
And make sure you
get the family to tell you
Everything they know, or
drag them into the station.
Yes, sir.
Neither ashley nor maggie seem
to know anything about florida,
Or anymore than they did before,
Though I do think
they talk to him.
Stephanie was the same,
but pamela's still or best bet.
Well, let's see then.
Hello.
Miss evonitz, this is
lieutenant rowland from...
From richland
sheriff's office, right.
I see your family's been
keeping you up to date.
Yeah.
Would that include
your brother, ma'am?
He called maybe two hours ago.
He wants me to meet him tonight,
Outside his favorite restaurant.
In bradenton?
Yeah, the pancake
griddle off us 41.
What time, ma'am?
This is sergeant
jennings with richland.
Yeah, we just called.
Our guy is headed
straight to you.
Kara, you can't
just go out into a,
A crowd full of strangers,
just you and jess and...
Mom, this is what we always do,
We go to the boy's
baseball game together.
We have a really
good time, that is it.
You can't know that.
Look, it's, kara,
it's just been a day.
You need to take some time.
I don't need time, mom.
I don't need time, I just
need everything to be normal.
Kara it is not.
He is still out there.
He is not here!
He's not here, I am!
I am right here.
I need to go back and do
the things that I usually do.
I need everything
to be normal, okay.
I am not gonna let him
take this away from me, too!
I need to do this.
I'm gonna do this.
I'm so sorry, I'm gonna do this.
Hey. Hey.
Officers be advised, fbi
units are now in position.
What's the chance
he's gonna show?
I guess we'll find
out in a minute.
Unit 1-1-3.
This is 1-1-3.
We got two sightings
of the suspect's vehicle.
Most recent turning
onto 16th, headed south.
He's coming your way.
I'll punch anybody
who looks at you funny.
It's gonna be okay. It's fine.
You just go get
good spots, okay,
And I'm gonna go wish
ryan good luck, like always.
Kara, you came?
Like I would miss a game.
That's why you're
the best girlfriend.
Hey.
You know you don't have to stay.
Good luck.
Dispatch, no
sign of the vehicle.
Wait.
Dispatch, we have
eyes on the suspect.
Go and apprehend, over.
Copy that.
Suspect is running
northbound on 16th.
Unit 1-1-3 in pursuit.
Now moving west on 52nd.
He just ran
straight into traffic.
Suspect's fled to
alley behind 56.
We still got him.
Still in pursuit.
Units 2-1-6 and 3-4
arriving from the west.
Be advised 1-1-3, over.
On deck, number nine.
I was there, you know, like at
the hospital when she came out.
She wouldn't let any man
touch her, not even her dad.
I cannot believe.
Hey, do you know me?
I didn't think so.
Woo!
Unit 1-1-3, do you
have a visual? Over.
Unit 1-1-3, where you at?
Unit 1-1-3.
Dispatch, we have the suspect.
Suspect is armed.
Requesting backup.
All units, repeat, all units,
Requesting canine to respond
to standoff with armed suspect.
Put down your weapon!
Drop it! It's over!
Drop your weapon!
Woo!
I said drop your
weapon! Okay, okay.
Put down your weapon!
Drop it! It's over!
Suspect is down.
We have a 10-56.
Appears deceased.
Kara, sweetheart,
rise and shine.
Hey, honey. Hey.
Good morning.
What's going on?
I made us some breakfast.
So, why don't you take a seat.
Wow, you never make breakfast,
And I'd much rather
know what's going on first.
Okay.
Well, sergeant jennings
will be here to explain more,
And if you have any questions,
But last night that
man killed himself.
So it's truly over now, honey.
You're safe.
Why didn't anyone tell me that?
I'm telling you now, sweetheart.
It happened last night?
Why didn't anyone tell me
that last night when it happened?
There was no reason to.
I should have know-,
what is it that you're trying
To protect me from?
You were having a nice time
at the game like you wanted,
So we didn't want to...
Hey there, kara.
If you think that I'm not
mad at you, I- no, I know.
You're absolutely
right to be mad.
If anyone deserved to know
what was happening it was you.
We should have
told you right away.
I should have known better.
I'm sorry I broke that trust.
You know, I'm not much
trained in this sort of thing.
But if I had to put money on it,
I'd say you weren't just
mad about the delay.
I'm mad at him.
I'm just so mad at him.
And all I've been
thinking about,
The only thing that's
been getting me through the
Interviews and the exams and
the people and everyone staring,
All I wanted was
just to get justice,
And I wanted him to go
to jail for a hundred years,
And I wanted him to rot there.
But only after I got to
stare him down in court,
And made him face me, and I
got to tell him about everything
That I remembered, and I'd let
him know that picking me was
The biggest mistake that
he's ever made in his life.
I don't know, I'm
just mad at him.
I shouldn't have
yelled at my mom.
That was messed up.
So now that there's no trial,
I don't have to tell
my story in court.
That's right.
And my mom and my dad and
ryan aren't gonna have to know
What actually, like, like
what actually happened.
And they're not gonna be hurt.
Well, it's for the best then.
You're a hero, kara.
I know it may not
always feel that way.
But the way you saved yourself,
The way you, even now,
are taking care of the people
You love, you're a hero.
I'd hire you for the
force in a heartbeat.
And as for evonitz, there is
no doubt he knew you were
His greatest mistake.
And I couldn't be
more proud of you for it.
Just give her some time.
She's processing a lot.
Can you give us a
second, sergeant jennings?
Of course.
I don't really feel like
a hug right now, mom.
Okay.
It's not because of, like...
I just feel like I
really want to do what
I feel like doing.
Of course, and I'm sorry.
I'm trying.
I don't know what to do.
I just really want
to be here for you.
I know you do, and I'm
gonna try to let you know
When you can be, okay.
But you can't change
what happened.
It happened.
But I'm still here.
I'm still me.
I survived.